http://fiatfinancial.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy and Notice
For the Fiat Financial Money Center LLC and any affiliates.
At Fiat Financial Money Center your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect and how we use that information and is applicable if you have applied for service with Fiat Financial Money Center, or if you are a current or former customer. This Privacy Policy is effective as of November 04, 2008.
PROTECTING THE PRIVACY OF CUSTOMER INFORMATION
We are committed to protecting your privacy and to implementing technology that gives you a powerful and secure online experience. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to transmit and store information about you. For instance, we use computer virus protection software, firewalls, and a 256 bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) for data transmission to secure your information. We are regularly evaluating new advances in security technology and techniques to provide protection for information about you. In addition, we permit only authorized employees who have a job-specific purpose and are trained in the proper handling of customer information to have access to your information.
INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU
We collect several types of information about you:
“Nonpublic Personal Information” you provide through on-line form, applications and registration forms, surveys, and or other entries, such as your name, address, telephone number, drivers’ license number or other government issued photo ID, social security number, email addresses, assets and income;
E-mail addresses of visitors that communicate with us via e-mails;
Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates or others, such as payment history and loan balances;
Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency, such as your creditworthiness and credit history;
Information we receive from third parties, such as your employer who may verify representations you made to us.
HOW WE USE INFORMATION WE COLLECT
The information we collect about you is used to provide services to you and contact you regarding administrative matters. We may also use your information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, and enforce our agreements with you, including, but not limited to the Terms and Conditions, Application Agreement, Loan Agreement and this Privacy Policy.
We may use your contact information to send you information about our company and promotional material. We may also use your personal, demographic and profile data to improve our website, for statistical analysis, for marketing and promotional purposes, and for editorial or feedback purposes for our advertisers. Information collected by us may be added to our databases and used for future e-mails or postal mailings regarding site updates, new products and services, upcoming events, and/or status of orders placed online, unless prohibited by law.
PARTIES TO WHOM WE DISCLOSE
We reserve the right to share data we collect with our affiliates, as well as to share, rent, sell, or otherwise disclose data we collect with non-affiliated third parties, including but not limited to magazine publishers, retailers, and direct marketers. Any non-affiliated third party we share, rent, sell, or otherwise disclose data to will be prescreened by us, determined by us to be reputable, and will use the personal data for marketing products and services which we determine, in our sole judgment, that you might find of interest.
Information we share with Affiliates:
Some of our services are provided using our affiliates, and we share nonpublic personal information with them in order to fulfill the services you have requested, and as required or permitted by law.
Information we share with Third Parties:
We use certain non-affiliated third parties as service providers, and we share nonpublic personal information with them in order to fulfill the services you have requested, and as required or permitted by law.
Information we share with Financial Institutions:
We may disclose information we collect to financial institutions with which we have a joint marketing and/or servicing agreements, such as banks.
CONTACT AND MARKETING PREFERENCES
Fiat Financial Money Center may contact you by several contact methods, including but not limited to: writing to you via US postal service and/or electronic mail, and calling you via telephone, at any address or number provided by you. We may also contact you via text messaging or other mobile communications device, if you have previously requested or agreed to this type of communication. We may use any one or all of these methods to contact you about the status or approval of your loan, inform you about special promotions, savings and services we believe may be of interest to you, to remind you of upcoming payments, and to communication with you regarding collections and other issues related to your loan.
You may manage your contact information and preferences by calling us at 888.992.0082, emailing us at customerservice@fiatfinancial.com. Notwithstanding the above, we reserve the right to contact you to inform you of technical service issues related to a service you requested. You will not be able to choose to unsubscribe from these communications as they are considered an essential part of the service you have requested. In addition, we reserve the right to contact you regarding your account status, collection matters, changes to subscriber agreements, privacy policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to you and/or your loan using any contact method described above.
ACCURACY OF YOUR ACCOUNT INFORMATION
We have established procedures to ensure that your financial information is accurate, current and complete, in keeping with reasonable industry standards. We continually strive to maintain complete and accurate information about you and your accounts. Should you ever believe that our records contain inaccurate or incomplete information about you, please notify us. We will investigate your concerns and correct any information we determine to be inaccurate.
CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
Because circumstances and technologies change, we reserve the right to change this policy at any time by notifying you of the existence and location of the new or revised privacy policy or by posting the changes online at our website.
WHO DO YOU CONTACT WITH QUESTIONS?
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices of this web site, please contact us by sending a letter to:
Fiat Financial Money Center
657 S 8th St
West Dundee IL 60118
Attn: Customer Service
Or (888) 992-0082
or
Sending us an e-mail at: customerservice@fiatfinancial.com.
Contact us our online loan company for more detailed information about any of the topics listed in our privacy policy. We serve clients throughout Illinois’s western and northwestern suburbs.
Apply for your loan today and get cash quickly.
2020 Fiat Financial Money Center. All rights reserved.
Website by web.com.
